motorsportreg.com 2007-12-29

# MotorsportReg.com : Privacy Policy

## Privacy First!

#### We treat your information as if it were our own

First and foremost understand that MotorsportReg.com, operated by [Pukka Software](http://www.pukkasoft.com/), works as hard as possible to protect your privacy as if it were our own. 

Because we gather certain types of information about MotorsportReg.com ("Pukka") users, we feel you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it. Questions regarding this policy should be directed to customer service. NOTE: Pukka cannot accept information from individuals who are under 16 years of age without first obtaining express parental consent. 

#### 1\. Capture and Use of Information

Registration 

If you participate in interactive activities (event registration, message boards, membership program, etc.) on Pukka, you may be asked to register for a free ID and password and/or to provide information on event registration forms. Unique identifiers, such as email addresses, IDs and passwords, are collected to verify your identity and for use as account numbers in our record system. Your contact information may also be used to contact you when necessary for customer service reasons. Financial information that is collected is used only to bill you for products and services that you specifically request. 

Cookies 

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Generally, cookies work by assigning to your computer a unique number that has no meaning outside of our site. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information; we use them to provide features such as personalization, to save your member ID and to keep track of your registration. We may also use cookies to assist us in delivering content specific to your interests. Additionally, after you've entered your member ID and password during a session on our service, we save that information so you don't have to re-enter it repeatedly during that session. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that. Not accepting cookies may make certain features of Pukka unavailable to you. 

IP Address 

We may use your IP address to identify you, to administer our Web site and to assist in diagnosing problems with our server. 

#### 2\. Additional Uses of Information

All of the information we collect, both what you tell us and what we collect through the use of cookies, is used to personalize your account, to customize our services and to allow our customer service representatives to contact you when necessary. It is Pukka's policy not to release any personally identifying information about you without your consent (usually obtained through an "opt-in" option that you may select when providing the information). In most cases, information will be released only on an aggregated basis (meaning that the information from many Pukka users is grouped together in a way that does not disclose the personal information of any particular user). 

By registering with our service, you give us permission to send you information about your account and our services from time to time or as requested by you. We also provide a number of opt-in mailing lists (such as our monthly calendar listings) that you may elect to receive. We may include promotional material in these correspondence but we will never sell, trade or otherwise make available your information to a third party without consent via an opt-in request, except in the event you make a purchase that requires fulfillment from a third party. 

Pukka may disclose information if we believe, in good faith, that it is necessary in order to: (a) comply with the law, (b) enforce the terms and conditions of this Agreement, or (c) protect the rights of you or us, to the extent that such disclosure is not otherwise prohibited by any law or regulation. 

#### 3\. General Privacy Information

Pukka may make various public forums or interactive areas (such as message boards, chat rooms or blogs) available to its users. When you disclose personal information in such public forums, that information can be collected and used by others in various ways, including by sending unsolicited messages. You are solely responsible for any postings you make on public forums on Pukka, and for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online. Further, the Pukka web site contains links to partners, advertisers and third party Internet sites and services that may collect data in connection with registrations, promotions, e-commerce, etc. Pukka is also linked to by certain partner web sites. Each of the web sites (linked from Pukka, or linking to Pukka) have separate privacy and data collection practices, independent of Pukka, and Pukka has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions and is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. We try our best to do business with reputable merchants but we cannot enforce nor endorse other company practices. 

Understand that registering for events will provide your complete personal profile to the organization running an event. While Pukka guarantees our usage of your information under this agreement, the organizations who use the Pukka services may have a different privacy policy and Pukka makes no guarantees about their use of your information. _This is the same situation as mailing a paper registration form to the organization._

#### 4\. Security

Pukka uses a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Personal information collected on Pukka is stored in a secure operating environment that is not available to the public. All credit card, checking account and registration information supplied by users is transmitted via industry-standard 128-bit Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. Pukka's technology department conducts frequent site-security audits.
